I don't want to go just yet.
Before the shuttle launches and I leave this world,
there's something I think you ought to know about me.
What is it, Ririko?
Everyone wants you to get really good at flirting with spirits
so you can make them fall in love with you.
And you're supposed to get better by practicing on me.
Yeah, that's the plan.
What about it?
Oh, it's just that I'm afraid.
I'm afraid I might be falling in love with you.
It's true.
We've known each other forever
and you've always treated me like a little sister.
But do you think you can start looking at me as a woman instead?
This is the best day ever!
Don't you worry about a thing.
I'll even wave to you from Jupiter.
It's not super far away.
Until next time, big brother.
Spirits.
Mysterious girls appearing from another world.
Should we fight against their pure strength with weapons of war
or should we address them with love?
Now, mankind is faced with the ultimate decision.
Star Wars
So
now
LROCK!
Dad! Mom!
Murigami!
Shen.
Yes, Reina?
Are you daydreaming again?
It's time to implement stage two of your training, so you better be ready.
Huh?
This is training?
Good afternoon, Shido.
Is there something I can help you with?
No, thank you.
What do you think you're doing?
Quit wasting everyone's time. Hurry up and make her fall in love with you.
Do I have to?
You ought to know by now that seducing a spirit is easier said than done.
If you can't even make a human love you, how do you expect to convince a spirit to?
You're asking the wrong guy. I'm not a stud.
We know. Just throw out a few compliments and see what happens.
If she responds well, we'll give you further instructions.
Um, is there something on your mind?
Miss Okamine, that's a cute outfit you're wearing.
What? Goodness, you really think so?
Oh my, that is very flattering of you.
Oh yes, it really does look good.
So does your hair and those sexy glasses.
Perfect shoes, perfect stockings, perfect attendance book.
Shido, is everything all right?
You got way too into that. Stop being creepy on you.
I'm kind of busy right now, so I'll see you in class.
This can be fixed.
All right, listen closely and do exactly as I say.
Here's the truth. I love homeroom. I look forward to going to it every day.
Well, that's nice to hear. I'm so glad that you like it.
The main reason is because I get to see you all the time. I can't help it. I think I've fallen in love with you.
Come on, don't say such silly things. Honestly, I'm flattered, but students and teachers can't love each other.
No, don't tell me that. I'm dead serious. I want to marry you.
You want to marry me?
Is it true? Once you're old enough to get married, I'll be in my 30s. Is that okay?
You need to meet my parents. Daddy gets so protected, but I think he'll like you.
He might even give us the house. Once you graduate and get a decent job, I can retire and start having babies.
Huh. We underestimated the enthusiasm of 29-year-old single women. They make for easy targets.
It'll be annoying if she gets more involved than necessary.
Hey, Shido, we're done here, so make up some excuses and get out of there pronto.
I'm really sorry, Miss Okamine. I don't think I'm ready for that level of commitment.
We can start out in an apartment and work our way up to a three-bedroom condo with a backyard.
And don't worry about wedding planning. I've been saving up for 15 years. You can take care of the DJ. I'll do the rest.
Could we tell Mo again to say that they get extra special?
You found a market with older women. Good to know.
Shut up!
How can you be so calm when I'm about to get...
Ah!
Oh, man. I'm sorry about that.
I'm all right.
Perfect timing. Why don't you practice with her, too?
Huh?
She's around the same age as you, so it'll be natural. Plus, even though she's not a spirit, she's a member of the A.S.T.
Doesn't seem like the type to spread rumors, either.
Spread rumors about what?
Just talk to her already!
Uh... Hey, Tomichi. Those clothes look nice on you. Where'd you get them?
It's a uniform.
Come on, idiot. You have to put in more effort than that. Again, with more feeling!
I don't know how.
Shin, follow my lead.
To be honest, I already know. I've known all about you for quite a while now.
I'm aware of that.
Oh, is that so? Nice. I'm real glad we're in the same class this semester. In fact, I watch you all the time during class when you study.
Yes, likewise.
Is that so? How random. I also like sneaking into your locker after school to sniff your gym clothes.
Same here.
Okay. I wasn't expecting that.
And why not?
Who knew we'd have so much in common, so do you want to go out with me?
That came out of nowhere? Don't you think this is a little sudden?
I wouldn't mind. I wouldn't mind going out with you.
Uh, cool. So, you want to, like, go somewhere with me? Something like that?
Like a movie?
I'm sorry. I assumed you were asking me out on a date, Shido. Am I wrong?
No, not at all. That's exactly what I meant.
Good.
Dang it! That's exactly what I meant! How come Reina didn't bail me out of that one? I'm screwed!
What's this?
For you, because you like my uniform.
Huh?
Your attention, please. This is not a drill. There have been precursory signs of an impending spatialquake in this vicinity.
Please evacuate.
Something just came up. Bye.
Hey, wait a second. Where are you going?
A spatialquake is about to happen. Head back to the Fraxinus for now.
Do you think it's a spirit?
Yes, princess. She'll be appearing at your exact location. Rise in high school.
They're on their way now. Roger that.
Here we go. The Quake has started.
Consider yourself lucky, Shido. The AST's CR units are deadly, but they weren't built for indoor combat.
As long as Princess remains inside the school, the AST will have a hard time interfering with whatever you do.
With what I do?
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
Relax. This is what you've been training for the past week. You're as ready as you'll ever be.
You want to save the spirit, or am I wrong?
She's right. I don't ever want to see that sad look on her face again.
Coterie, you're absolutely sure I can do this?
Yes, just believe in yourself. You represent a different way of dealing with the spirits. A more intimate method. Remember that.
Be friendly with them, you sweet talk, and make them fall for me.
You're gonna do just fine. Besides, the Fraxinus has got your back.
Behold the pride of Rattattusker, ready to respond to any circumstance.
With five marriages and five divorces under his belt, the love master. Bad marriage, go on the way.
Mmm. Hey there.
It's the working girl's favorite midnight client.
CEO, Mikimoto.
Who doesn't love love?
Go after this lady's fella and you'll regret it.
Don't you dare piss her off.
Nail knocker, Shiizaki.
The man with no fewer than a hundred wives.
Dimension breaker, Nakatsugawa.
A-okay.
Lastly, a woman whose love is so strong, not even a silly restraining order can keep her away.
Deep love, Minowa!
Okay.
Fantastic. I'm relying on perverts.
Don't worry. Everyone is good at what they do.
And that's only a portion of the troops on our side. Just stay calm.
Even if you die once, you can always start a new game without a penalty.
I'm pretty sure this isn't a game.
Have faith in your little sister. Now get in there and flirt!
Wait just a minute. I don't want to fight with you. Please, listen to me.
What's your name? And why are you following me?
Because...
Don't answer yet!
There has been a change in the mental state of the spirit.
Reaction analysis complete.
Displaying choices on screen.
My name is Shido Itsuka. I've come to save you.
I'm just a passerby! Please don't kill me!
Before asking someone's name, you should give your own.
Well, there they are. Now everyone get to work!
No surprise here. You guys went with the same one I did.
The first choice is a tried and true classic, but it doesn't apply in the situation.
And it does sound a little cliché.
Option two is also out. If he escapes, he can't continue the conversation.
Number three it is.
I agree. In this case, three makes the most sense. She'll let him live and he'll get to know her better.
Okay, Shido, we've made up your mind. Now listen closely and then repeat after me.
What are you waiting for? Answer the question already!
Before asking for someone's name...
You should really give your own first!
I hate you, Yonori!
Well, that was unexpected.
Unexpected my ass! I could have been dead!
No more time for games. If you do not answer me, I can only assume you are my enemy.
My name is Shido Ichika. I'm a student at this school. I've got no reason to bite you!
Hold on. This isn't the first time we've crossed paths.
No, it's not. I saw you on the 10th in the city.
That's right. I thought so. I remember you saying something odd to me that day.
You said you didn't come to kill me and that you couldn't kill anyone. And now I know that was a lie. Why else would you be here?
Your face. How come you always look so sad?
I'm not trying to do anything. And it's true. I really have no reason to kill you.
Quit lying! Every single human is out to get me. I haven't done a thing to them, yet they want me dead.
I swear that's not true!
You never answered me. You claim to have no intention of killing anyone. If that's really the truth, tell me why it is you came here.
Her first reaction wasn't all that pretty. This time option one's probably the safest choice.
I... I wanted to meet you.
To meet me? Why would you want that?
Do you guys have any ideas?
I recommend a straightforward approach.
Yeah, be clear and direct. This girl's way too dense to get anything subtle.
That's a good point. We've already wasted enough time answering all these questions.
Uh, it's simple. I came here because I'm interested in you.
I'm in no mood to joke around.
I know. And neither am I.
You want to know the truth? I came here so I could talk to you.
I don't even care what we talk about. Not one bit. You can ignore me if you want to.
But know this. I'm not like every other human. Because...
Stop it! Wait for our signal!
Because I'll never let you down!
You said your name was Shido, right? And when you said you were interested in me, were you being serious?
Yes, I was.
But like serious, serious?
Serious, serious.
100% serious, serious?
1000% serious, serious!
Jerk! Who would seriously fall for your amateur tricks? Stupid dummy!
But that was from the heart!
Then again, this is different. I still don't know what your intentions are. But you are the only human I've ever had a normal conversation with.
You know this world which could serve me well. It might just work.
Yep, it's settled. This should prove your usefulness.
Thanks, I guess. Oh yeah, what was your name again?
My name? I've never had one of those. But I suppose I will need one if I want to find out why humans are so awful.
Okay, why don't you come up with something you can call me?
Well, she's certainly putting the Fraxness to work, isn't she?
Alright crew, we need to think of a name on the double!
The few suggestions we have aren't gonna be enough. Do you want to call in the troops from around the world?
One step ahead of you.
Huh? Gosh, now what does she want?
Your wish is my command, my digital darling.
Isn't that that fool, Tanamachi?
He's probably sending a dirty text to Shido.
That's so lame.
Come on, man! We're not naming Princess after one of your ex-wives!
I don't even know how to pronounce that gibberish!
It's Clarabelle.
The 1920s are over. Can't anyone here think of a halfway decent girl's name?
What about Tomei?
Tomei? Tomei sounds kinda neat, right?
Wow, she's bad. Is Tomei that bad?
Don't think I can't tell what a human is attempting to make fun of me, you got it?
Okay, just a minute. Apologies to anyone named Tomei, but I don't think I know a single girl that would like that name.
Thanks, Shido. There has to be a perfect name for her. How about Touka?
Touka? Yeah, I guess that'll work.
Is this how it's written?
It is.
Huh.
Touka. Now I have a name. I think I like it. Thank you.
Yeah, yeah, you're welcome.
Touka just means tenth as in the day we met, but hey, it's not like she'll ever need to know that.
Get down and take cover!
Are you sure this is okay, Captain?
We have permission to smoke them out. Once we've done our job, the reinforcements can take care of the rest.
Are you alright?
Hurry up and leave while you still can.
I'd love to continue our talk, but the last thing I want is for you to get hurt.
Don't just stand there. Get going before they open fire!
I'm staying right here.
Sit down. I want to talk some more.
You want to know about this world, don't you? So have a seat.
Pretend they're not even here.
Alright.
I'm curious. If you're not human, what exactly are you?
I don't know. I don't remember how long ago it was when I appeared out of nowhere. That's all I can recall. Most of my oldest memories are fuzzy and distorted. I honestly don't know what kind of being I am.
That's awful.
I suppose so. My birth was sudden. I don't know how long ago it was when I appeared out of nowhere. That's all I can recall. Most of my oldest memories are fuzzy and distorted.
I honestly don't know what kind of being I am.
That's awful.
I suppose so. My birth was sudden and inexplicable and the Mecha Mecha Squad was already in the air when I awoke.
Mecha Mecha, huh?
Them. The noisy flying people.
Interesting.
Here's your chance.
Her happiness meter is over 70. Now's as good a time as any to make a move.
What are you all doing?
I don't know how long ago it was when I appeared out of nowhere. That's all I can recall. Most of my oldest memories are fuzzy and distorted. I honestly don't know what kind of being I am.
That's awful.
I suppose so. My birth was sudden and inexplicable and the Mecha Mecha Squad was already in the air when I awoke.
Mecha Mecha, huh?
Them. The noisy flying people.
Interesting.
Here's your chance. Her happiness meter is over 70. Now's as good a time as any to make a move.
What do you want me to do?
For starters, you could ask her out on a date.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just itchy.
You've been muttering under your breath for a while.
Are you hiding something from me?
No, no, you're overreacting.
Then tell me what you were saying just now.
I forgot?
Come on. Cut to the chase and ask her out.
Ask her out!
Alright already, shut up, I'll do it!
Toka, I want to ask you something.
But it's... well, it's kind of abrupt.
But will you go out on a date with me?
with me have we received any new orders origami that's a negative ma'am even after all this
wait a minute someone is down there with the spirit hold on hold your fire
origami get back here what exactly is a date you don't know
what tobichi stand back well if it isn't you again he's not your shield you scum you've got it all wrong
what are you doing origami we don't have orders to break in on foot sandal bond
shito get out of there now the fraxinus will come to retrieve you and leave her here alone
you could have been killed out there do you realize just how lucky you are she became lost
exercise some restraint okay you're a valuable member of the ast so start acting like it
i was there when everything happened still the massive destruction just doesn't seem real
but yesterday was real it wasn't a dream at all shito that's right i really did talk with toka and
give her a name hey quit ignoring me
toka you just now noticed me wow you are so dumb but how did you end up back over here
the spatial alarm didn't even go off why would it you were the one who invited me back for a date
i think well guess what it's time for that date let's go let's go let's go let's go let's go
okay just bring it down a bit and you should probably get out of that first do you mind
changing right now you want me to undress in broad daylight no that's not it
let me show you an example you think this outfit is better why are you walking around with this
picture quit asking questions just change already very well
how does this look um good glad you think so time for our date
uh
two
Oh
Hey, stop walking so fast. You're too slow, Shido. Daytime, daytime. Oh, sure. Just announce it to the entire world.